{
    "subject": "Bernd_von_Beyenbach",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Carla_von_Lahnstein",
    "human_readable": "Bernd von Beyenbach is married to Carla von Lahnstein.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9881086945533752,
            "question": "Is there a marriage between Bernd von Beyenbach and Carla von Lahnstein?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.956214964389801,
            "question": "Is Bernd von Beyenbach related to Carla von Lahnstein?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9394491314888,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Bernd von Beyenbach and Carla von Lahnstein?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9309751987457275,
            "question": "To whom is Carla von Lahnstein married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9280745387077332,
            "question": "Who is married to Carla von Lahnstein?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9080482721328735,
            "question": "What can you tell me about the relationship between Bernd von Beyenbach and Carla von Lahnstein?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8922861814498901,
            "question": "Are Bernd von Beyenbach and Carla von Lahnstein partners?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.889458179473877,
            "question": "Name the spouse of Carla von Lahnstein."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8284424543380737,
            "question": "Who is Bernd von Beyenbach?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6880990862846375,
            "question": "Do Bernd von Beyenbach and Carla von Lahnstein have a familial connection?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Bernd von Beyenbach is married to Carla von Lahnstein.",
            "html": "yago_13082_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Bernd von Beyenbach?",
            "html": "yago_13082_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name the spouse of Carla von Lahnstein.",
            "html": "yago_13082_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are Bernd von Beyenbach and Carla von Lahnstein partners?",
            "html": "yago_13082_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_13082_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_13082_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_13082_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_13082_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_13082_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_13082_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_13082_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_13082_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_13082_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_13082_5.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nWhile the documents state that Carla was initially married to Bernd von Beyenbach, they also mention that their marriage was of convenience and ended in divorce. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I can conclude that:\n\n* The documents describe Carla von Lahnstein as a fictional character on German soap opera \"Verbotene Liebe\".\n* Bernd von Beyenbach is mentioned in the documents as one of Carla's spouses, with their marriage being described.\n* However, upon closer inspection, it appears that Carla and Bernd's marriage is not portrayed as a romantic or loving relationship, but rather as a marriage of convenience. Additionally, Carla has already been married to Susanne Brandner.\n\nGiven this information, the answer would be:\n\n{'output': 'no'}\n\nThis indicates that the statement \"Bernd von Beyenbach is married to Carla von Lahnstein\" may not accurately reflect the context and relationships described in the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"no\"}\n```\n\nExplanation:\nThe documents mention that Carla von Lahnstein was previously married to Bernd von Beyenbach, but they divorced. There's no information indicating that they are currently married. Therefore, the statement \"Bernd von Beyenbach is married to Carla von Lahnstein\" is not supported by the provided documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}